pornnic.com 2003-04-10

# 

                                                                                      Toll-Free Phone: 1-866-40-SEXCO
                                                                                      Toll-Free Fax: 1-866-50-SEXCO
                                                                                      E-Mail:                law@sexco.net
Privacy Notice                                                                                     WWW.SEXCO.NET
Sexco knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so
carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting Sexco, you are accepting the practices
described in this Privacy Notice.
What Personal Information About Customers Does Sexco Gather?
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Sexco.
Here are the types of information we gather:
    •    Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other
         way. Scroll to the bottom of this page to see examples of what we collect. You can choose not to provide certain
         information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that
         you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our
         stores, and communicating with you.
    •    Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For
         example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser
         accesses Sexco. Scroll to the bottom of this page to see examples of the information we receive. A number of
         companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide
         you with a personalized experience at Sexco if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools
         exist.
    •    E-mail Communications: To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation
         when you open e-mail from Sexco if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to
         lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do
         not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your Accounts Manager.
    •    Information from Other Sources: For reasons such as improving personalization of our service (for example,
         providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we might receive
         information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated
         delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver
         your next purchase or communication more easily.
What About Cookies?
    •    Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to
         enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as storage of items in your Shopping Cart
         between visits.
    •    The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new
         cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.
         However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of Sexco 's coolest features, and we recommend that you
         leave them turned on.

Does Sexco Share the Information It Receives?
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We
share customer information only with the subsidiaries Sexco, controls and as described below:
    •    Agents: We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling
         orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists,
         analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service.
         They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
    •    Promotional Offers: Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of Sexco customers on behalf of other
         businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. If you do not want to receive such
         offers, please adjust your Accounts Manager.
    •    Business Transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores or assets. In such
         transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that
         Sexco, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred
         assets.
    •    Protection of Sexco and Others: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is
         appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights,
         property, or safety of Sexco, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and
         organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
    •    With Your Consent: Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to
         third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.
How Secure Is Information About Me?
    •    We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using 128 bit Secure Sockets Layer
         (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.
    •    We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the
         entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.
    •    It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign
         off when finished using a shared computer.
What Information Can I Access?
Sexco gives you access to the following information about you for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases,
updating that information. This list will change as our Web site evolves.
    •    Your Account Manager
What Choices Do I Have?
    •    As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a
         purchase or to take advantage of such Sexco features as Your Accounts Manager.
    •    You can add or update certain information on pages such as those listed in the "What Information Can I Access?"
         section above. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.
    •    If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your Account Manager. (If you do not want
         to receive Conditions of Use and other legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Notice, those notices will still
         govern your use of Sexco, and it is your responsibility to review them for changes.)

     •    The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new
          cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.
     •    In addition, the Federal Trade Commission provides useful information about online privacy on its own Web site,
          Site Seeing on the Internet.
Children
Sexco does not sell products for purchase by children.
Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions
If you choose to visit Sexco, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use,
including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the Province of British Columbia. If
you have any concern about privacy at Sexco, please send us a thorough description to webmaster@sexco.net, and we will try
to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also, and use of information
that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our
notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent
changes.
Related Practices and Information
     •    Conditions of Use
     •    All Rights Reserved
     •    Affiliates Program Terms & Conditions
     •    Adult Website Turnkey Agreement
     •    Adult Web Hosting Agreement
     •    Adult Web Content Agreement
Automatic Information
Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer
to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version,
operating system, and platform; purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through, and
from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; products you viewed or searched and phone number used to call
our 800 number.
  Copyright © 2002. Sexco™ is a subsidiary of Internet PM - #3-415 Dunedin Street, Victoria, BC V8T 5G8
